各位 我想给你们介绍一个人
Guys? There's, uh, somebody I'd like you to meet.
等等 那是什么?
W-wait. What is that?
这是马赛尔 要打声招呼吗?      我不要
That would be Marcel. You wanna say hi?        No. No, I don't.
他很珍贵 你从哪里得到他的?
Oh, he is precious. Where did you get him?
我朋友贝瑟把他从实验室救出来的
My friend Bethel rescued him from some lab.
真残忍
That is so cruel.
怎么会有父母把孩子取名叫贝瑟?
Why? Why would a parent name their child Bethel?
那猴子的屁股上长了个罗斯
Hey, that monkey's got a Ross on its ass.
罗斯 它要和你同住吗?
Ross, is he gonna live with you, like, in your apartment?
对 卡萝离开后家里冷冷清清的
Yeah. I mean, it's been kind of quiet since Carol left, so
为什么不找个室友?
Why don't you just get a roommate?
不知道 我觉得人到了某种年纪
Ah, I don't know. I think you reach a certain age
跟室友住有点可悲
having a roommate is kind of pathe, uh,
抱歉 我的意思是 在梵语中表示很酷的生活方式
sorry, that's "pathet", which is Sanskrit for "really cool way to live".
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
《老友记》蓝光版 第01季 第10集
猴子.The One With the Monkey
调校制作：寒 枫
字幕编辑：悠悠慕雪
各位 我今晚唱的都是新写的歌
Hey guys, I'm doing all new material tonight.
十二首关于我妈自杀的新歌
I have 12 new songs about my mother's suicide
一首关于雪人的歌
and one about a snowman.
你最好先唱雪人
Might want to open with the snowman.
嘿 乔伊      嗨
Hey, Joey.        Hey, buddy.
结果怎么样?
So, how'd it go?
我没得到那份工作
Ah, I didn't get the job.
怎么可能? 你是去年的圣诞老人
How could you not get it? You were Santa last year.
我不知道 某个胖子跟店经理有一腿
I don't know. Some fat guy's sleeping with the store manager.
他根本无法逗人开心 这就是政治
He's not even jolly. It's all political.
那你要当什么?
So, what are you gonna be?
我会当他的助手之一
Ah, I'm gonna be one of his helpers.
真是个耻辱
It's just such a slap in the face, you know?
你们打算怎么过新年?
Hey, do you guys know what you're doing for New Year's?
怎么?新年有什么问题吗?
Gee, what? What is wrong with New Year's?
你是没有 你有保罗
Nothing for you. You have Paolo.
你不用面对那可怕的节日压力
You don't have to face the horrible pressures of this holiday
急需寻找有嘴唇的生物
desperate scramble to find anything with lips
在球落下的那一刻 有个可以亲吻的对象 我真大声
just so can have someone to kiss when the ball drops. Man,I'm talking loud.
好吧 新年时保罗会在罗马
Well, for your information, Paolo's gonna be in Rome this New Year.
所以我会跟你们一样可悲
So I'll be just as pathetic as the rest of you.
你想得美
Yeah, you wish.
我受够了迪克拉克的节日疲劳轰炸
It's just that I'm sick of being a victim of this Dick Clark holiday.
我提议 今年我们不约会 做个约定
I say this year, no dates, we make a pact.
就我们六个人一起吃晚餐
Just the six of us. Dinner
好啊      同意
Yeah, okay.        Alright.
我希望大家能更热烈一点
You know, I was hoping for a little more enthusiasm.
好耶!
Woo! Yeah!
菲比 到你了      好的
Phoebe, you're on.        Oh. Oh, good.
各位 应观众热烈的要求
Okay, hi. Ladies and gentlemen, back by popular demand
欢迎菲比布非小姐
Miss Phoebe Buffay. Wooh!
谢谢大家
Thanks. Hi.
首先我想先唱首 这个节日对我意义重大的歌曲
Urn, I want to start with a song that means a lot to me this time of year.
我做了一个人 眼睛是煤炭做的
I made a man with eyes of coal
他有谜样的微笑
And a smile so bewitchin'
我要怎么承受
How was I supposed to know
我母亲死在厨房的事实?
That my mom was dead in the kitchen?
啦啦啦...
Lalala...
母亲的骨灰
My mother's ashes
甚至是她的睫毛
Even her eyelashes
安放在一个黄色的小坛子
Are resting in a little yellow jar
有时天寒地冻      我是老实说
And sometimes when it's freezing        I'm being honest here.
你不同意
You don't agree.
我有点想打喷嚏      你说得没错
I feel a little sneezy.        You're right.
现在我      不好意思 抱歉
And now I...        Excuse me? Excuse me?
吵闹的两位
Yeah, noisy boys.
你们有什么想跟大家分享吗?
Is it something that you'd like to share with the entire group?
没有 没事
No. No, that's that's okay.
如果有事如此重要 你们非得在我演唱时讨论
Well, come on, if it's important enough to discuss while I'm playing
那就重要到和大家分享
then I assume it's important enough for everyone else to hear
那家伙回家后一定会记得这教训
That guy's going home with a note.
没事 我只是说      请你大声点行吗?
No. I was, I was just saying to my        Could you speak up please?
抱歉
Sorry.
我只是在跟朋友说 你是我见过的最美丽的姑娘
I wa, I was just saying to my friend that I thought you were the most beautiful woman that I'd ever seen in my life.
他说黛瑞汉娜      黛瑞汉娜
And then he said that you said you thought        Darryl Hannah.
黛瑞汉娜是他见过最漂亮的女人
Daryl Hannah was the most beautiful woman that he'd ever seen in his life.
我说 我喜欢她在"美人鱼"的演出
And I said, yeah, I liked her in Splash, a lot,
"华尔街"就一般般了
but not so much in in Wall Street.
她有种...      强硬特质
I thought she had kind of a        Hard quality.
黛瑞汉娜是传统的美
And, uh, while Daryl Hannah is beautiful in a conventional way,
你则是散发出高雅的气质
you are, uh, luminous with a kind of delicate grace.
然后你就开始大吼了
Then uh, that, that, that's when you started yelling.
好 我们休息一会
Okay, we're gonna take a short break.
那家伙带回家的不只是教训而已
Hey, that guy's going home with more than a note.
过来 马赛尔 坐这
Come here, Marcel. Sit here.
菲比 我真不敢相信他还没吻你
Pheebs I can't believe he hasn't kissed you yet.
到我和保罗第六次约会时
I mean, God, by my sixth date with Paolo...
他就已经给我的胸部取名字了
I mean, he had already named both my breasts.
我是不是分享太多了?
Ooh, did I just share too much?
一点点
Just a smidge.
大卫是个科学家 做事一丝不苟
Davids, like, you know, scientist guy. He's very methodical.
我觉得很浪漫      我也这么觉得
I think it's romantic.        Me too. Oh!
你们看过"军官与绅士"吗?
Did you ever see An Officer and a Gentleman?
嗯
Yeah.
他就像陪我去看那部电影的男生
Well, he's kind of like the guy I went to see that with.
除了
Except
他更聪明 温柔 而且贴心
Except he's smarter, and gentler, and sweeter
我只想一直和他在一起
I just, I just want to be with him all the time.
日以继夜 夜以继日
Day and night. And night and day.
还有特别的日子
And special occasions.
等等 我明白了 你要邀请他一起过新年 对不对?
Wait a minute, wait, I see where this is going. You're gonna ask him to New Year's. Aren't you?
你要毁约! 她要抛弃我们!
You're gonna break the pact. She's gonna break the pact.
不 不 不 不 不 不
No, no, no, no, no, no.
好吧 我可以毁约吗?
Yeah, could I just?
好吧 因为我已经邀请了珍妮丝      什么?!
Yeah, 'cause I already asked Janice.        What?!
拜托 这是你定的约定啊
Come on, this was a pact. This was your pact.
我耐不住寂寞 我毁约了
I snapped, okay? I couldn't handle the pressure and I snapped.
可是 珍妮丝? 你们的分手糟透了
Yeah, but Janice? That that was like the worst breakup in history.
我不是说这是好主意 我只是说我毁约了
I'm not saying it was a good idea. I'm saying I snapped.
不好意思我迟到了
Hi. Hi, sorry I'm late.
太可笑了
Too many jokes.
一定要取笑乔伊
Must mock Joey.
很棒的鞋子吧?
Nice shoes, huh?
我快笑死了
Aah, you're killing me.
罗斯 他又在玩我的锅铲了
Ross. He's playing with my spatulas again.
他又不会玩坏的 不是吗?
Look, he's not gonna hurt them, right?
你一定要把他带来这里吗?
Do you always have to bring him here?
我不想把他单独留在家
Look, I didn't wanna leave him alone. Alright?
我们今早吵了第一次架
We, we had our first fight this morning.
我觉得是因为我加班的关系 我说了不该说的话
I think it has to do with my working late. I said some things that I didn't mean.
然后他就朝我扔了一坨屎
he threw some faeces.
你加班时我可以替你照顾他
You know, if you're gonna work late, I could look in on him for you.
太好了 好
Oh, that would be great. Okay.
但是如果你去 一定要假装你是去找他
But if you do, make sure it seems like you're there to see him, okay?
而不是帮我忙
And you're not, like doing it as a favor to me.
好 但是他如果问 我就要实话实说了
Okay. But if he asks, I'm not going to lie.
但仍无法测试这个理论
But you can't actually test this theory.
因为现今粒子加速器的速度
Because today's particle accelerators are nowhere near powerful enough
仍无法模拟出这样的情况
to simulate these conditions.
好 那我有个问题      请说
Okay. Alright. I have a question then.        Yeah.
你打算吻我吗?
Were you planning on kissing me ever?
非常合理的问题
Uh,that's definitely a valid question
答案是
and, uh, the answer
是的
would be yes.
我有这个打算
Yes I was.
但我要这非凡的吻
But see, I wanted it to be this phenomenal kiss
发生在非凡的时刻 因为是你
that happened at this phenomenal moment, because, well, it's you.
当然
Sure.
对 但是等得越久 这个吻就越非凡
Right. But, see, the longer I waited, the more phenomenal the kiss had to be.
此时此刻
And now, we've reached a place
我只想
where it's just gotta be one of those things where I just like...
扫去桌上的一切 把你丢上去
sweep everything off the table and throw you down on it.
而我不是会扫去一切的那种猴急的人
And, uh, I'm not really a, uh, sweeping sort of fella.
大卫 我认为你正是那样的人
Oh, David, I, I think you are a sweeping sort of fella.
我的意思是 你是个猛男!
I mean, you're a sweeper!
只是被困在物理学家的体内
Trapped inside a physicist's body.
是吗?      没错 我肯定
Really?        Oh, yeah. Oh, I'm sure of it.
来吧 扫掉一切 把我丢上去
You should just do it. Just sweep and throw me.
现在?      就是现在
Now? Now?        Oh yeah, right now.
好
Okay. Okay, okay.
嗯 这个很贵
You know what? This was just really expensive.
这个是礼物
And I'll take, this was a gift.
好吧 你现在比较像在打扫      额 管他的
Okay, now you're just kind of tidying.        Okay, what the hell? What the hell?
你想要我把你丢上去还是你自己跳?
You want me to actually throw you or you, you wanna just hop?
我可以跳
I can hop.
告诉我 "不约会的约定" 对你们有何意义?
So tell me something, what does the phase "no date pact" mean to you?
真的很抱歉
I'm sorry, okay?
只是钱德约了人 菲比也约了人
It's just that Chandler has somebody and Phoebe has somebody.
我就想邀请搞笑巴比
I thought I'd ask Fun Bobby.
搞笑巴比? 你的前男友搞笑巴比?      对
Fun Bobby, your exboyfriend, Fun Bobby?        Yeah.
你还知道其他的搞笑巴比吗?
You know more than one Fun Bobby?
我刚好认识一个搞笑巴伯
I happen to know a Fun Bob.
好了
Okay. Here we go.
没有地方加牛奶了
Whoa, whoa, whoa. There's no room for milk.
好了 现在有了
There. Now there is.
所以在没有约会的夜晚
Okay, so on our no date evening
三个人都有约会了
three of you now are gonna to have dates.
额 四个      四个
Uh, four.        Four.
五个      五个
Five.        Five.
抱歉 保罗提早搭飞机回来
Sorry. Paolo's catching an earlier flight.
我在店里遇见一位很性感的单身妈妈
Yeah. And I met this really hot single mom at the store. Ha, ha.
我这个小精灵怎能抗拒?
What's an elf to do?
所以只有我 孤单一人
Okay, so I'm gonna be the only one standing there alone...
当球落下的时候?
when the ball drops?
别这样 我们会办个大派对 没人会知道谁是谁
Oh. come on. We'll have a big party, and no one will know who's with who.
我现在真的不需要知道这些
Hey, you know, this is so not what I needed right now.
怎么了?      噢 是马赛尔
What's the matter?        Oh, it's, it's Marcel.
他一直拒我于门外
He keeps shutting me out, you know?
老是拖着双手不断绕圈子
He's walking around all the time, dragging his hands.
太奇怪了 我前几晚还跟他玩得很开心
That's so weird. I had such a blast with him the other night.
是吗?      是啊 我们一起玩 还看电视
Really?        Yeah, we played. We watched TV.
杂耍那部分实在太精彩了
That juggling thing is amazing.
什么?
What, uh...?
什么杂耍?
What juggling thing?
拿袜子当球耍啊 我以为是你教的
With the balled up socks? I figured you taught him that.
不是
No.
其实没什么大不了的 只是拿袜子当球耍而已
You know, it wasn't that big a deal. He just balled up socks.
还有一颗香瓜
And a melon.
菲比 嗨      嗨 麦克斯 你认识大家了吗?
Phoebe. Hi.        Hi Max. Hey, do you know everybody?
不认识 你看到大卫了吗?
No. Have you seen David?
没有 他不在
No, he hasn't been around.
如果看到他 叫他打包 我们要去明斯克了
Well, if you see him, tell him to pack his bags. We are going to Minsk.
明斯克?      明斯克 在俄罗斯
Minsk?        Minsk. It's in Russia.
我知道明斯克在哪里
I know where Minsk is.
我们申请到奖助金
Ha, ha. We got the grant.
全额赞助我们三年
Three years, all expenses paid.
你们什么时候走?
So when, when do you leave?
一月一号
January first.
哈罗?
Hello?
嘿 嗨      嗨
Hey.        Hi.
你怎么来了?      麦克斯跟我说了明斯克的事
Hi, what are you doing here?        Urn, well, Max told me about Minsk.
我是来恭喜你的 太令人兴奋了
So, congratulations! This is so exciting!
如果我们能去就更兴奋了
It'd be even more exciting if we were going.
你们不去?为什么?
Oh, you're not going? Oh, why?
跟她说啊 大卫
Tell her, David.
"我不想去明斯克
"I don't wanna go to Minsk
和李波森 亚马古基还有法兰克工作
to work with Lipson and Yamaguchi and Flank.
不 我想留在这里 和我的女友亲热"
No, no, no. I wanna stay here and make out with my girlfriend!!"
好了 谢谢你 麦克斯
Okay, thank you, Max. Thank you.
那你真的不去吗?
So, so you're really not going?
我不知道 我不知道怎么办
I don't know. I don't know what I'm gonna do. I just
你来决定
You decide.
别这样      求你了
Oh, don't do that.        Please?
我在求你 我无法做决定
No. but I'm asking. I can't make a decision.
我不能 拜托你      好吧 留下来
I can't. Please, just        Okay. Stay.
留下来      留下来
Stay.        Stay.
你越来越厉害了
Getting so good at that.
都是麦克斯的东西
It was Max's stuff.
我喜欢菊芋
I love this artichoke thing.
不要告诉我里面是什么 我明天才开始节食
Oh. Don't tell me what's in it. The diet starts tomorrow.
你还记得珍妮丝吧?
You remember Janice.
历历在目
Vividly.
嗨      嗨 我是珊蒂
Hi.        Hi, I'm Sandy.
珊蒂 嗨 请进
Sandy, hi. Come on in.
你把孩子带来了?      对 可以吧?
You brought your kids.        Yeah. That's okay, right?
派对
Party.
那个东西不能进来
That thing is not coming in here.
"那个东西"? 你是这样接待客人的吗?
"That thin"? This is how you greet guests at a party?
我问问你 如果我是和我的新女友来
Let me ask you something. If I showed up here with my new girlfriend
你也不欢迎她么?
she wouldn't be welcome in your home?
你的新女友不会在我的咖啡桌上尿尿
I'm guessing your new girlfriend wouldn't urinate on my coffee table.
这事他比任何人都尴尬
Okay. He was more embarrassed about that than anyone.
好吗? 他鼓足勇气回到这儿
Okay? And for him to have the courage to walk back in here
假装什么都没发生过
like nothing happened
好吧 不要让他靠近我就好了
All right. All right. Just keep him away from me.
谢了 来吧 马赛尔
Thank you. Come on, Marcel.
咱们去交际一下吧
What do you say you and I do a little mingling?
那好 我们待会儿见
All right, I'll, uh, catch up with you later.
天啊 瑞秋
Oh, my gosh. Rachel, honey
你还好吧?保罗呢?
Are you okay? Where's Paolo?
罗马 那混蛋没赶上飞机
Rome. Jerk missed his flight.
然后你的脸就爆炸了?
And then your face exploded?
不是
No. Okay.
我在机场 正准备上出租车
I was at the airport, getting into a cab
有个女人
when this woman
带着笔记本的金发女人
this blond planet with a pocketbook
开始对我大吼
starts yelling at me.
说她先叫到出租车
Something about how it was her cab first.
我还没反应过来 她就开始扯我的头发
And then the next thing I know, she just starts, starts pulling me out by my hair.
我拿出口哨猛吹
So I'm blowing my attack whistle thingy
又来了三辆出租车
and three more cabs show up.
我正要进出租时 她又绊我
and as I'm going to get into a cab, she tackles me.
然后我撞到了路边 嘴唇被哨子割伤
And I hit my head on the curb and cut my lip on my whistle.
哦 大家在派对玩得好吗?
Oh! Everybody having fun at the party?
有人吃我做的蘸酱吗?
Are people eating my dip?
我上周在店里看到你时
You know, when I saw you at the store last week
大概是我第一次 在心里脱掉小精灵的衣服
it was probably the first time I ever mentally undressed an elf.
哇 真淫荡
Wow, that's, uh, dirty.
对
Yeah.
嘿 孩子们
Hey, kids.
看看他 我不要求他整晚陪我
Look at him. I'm not saying he has to spend the whole evening with me
但至少关心我一下
but at least check in.
你在这儿啊
There you are.
你从我身边跑掉了
You got away from me.
但被你找到了
But you found me.
罗斯 帮我们照张相
Here, Ross, take our picture.
笑一个 你在珍妮丝的相机里了
Smile. You're on Janice Camera.
现在就杀了我 杀了我
Kill me. Kill me now. Ha, ha.
各位 搞笑巴比来了
Hey everybody, it's Fun Bobby!
搞笑巴比
Fun Bobby
嘿 巴比
Hey, Bobby.
嘿 不好意思我迟到了 但是我祖父
Hey, sorry I'm late. But my, uh, grandfather
他两个小时前去世了
he died about two hours ago.
但是明天才有飞机 所以...
But I, I, I couldn't get a flight out till tomorrow, so
我就来了
here I am.
嘿 搞笑巴比 你好吗?
Hey, Fun Bobby. How's it going, man?
哇 谁死了?
Whoa. Who died?
他的棺材暂时不盖上
It's going to be an open casket, you know?
所以我至少能再见他最后一面
So at least I'll, I get to see him again.
我要把照片放大 标题写上"破镜重圆"
I'm gonna blow this one up and I'm gonna write "Reunited" in glitter.
好了 珍妮丝 够了
All right, Janice, that's it!
珍妮丝?珍妮丝?
Janice? Janice? Ahem.
嘿 珍妮丝?
Hey, Janice?
我请你来这个派对 并不代表我们
When I invited you to this party, I didn't necessarily think it meant that we
噢 不
Oh, no.
不会吧
很抱歉让你误会了      天哪
I'm sorry you misunderstood.        Oh, my God.
你听我说 钱德 你听我说
You listen to me, Chandler, you listen to me.
这可能是你和我最后一次在一起了
One of these times is just gonna be your last chance with me.
赶快给我那东西
Oh, will you give me the thing?
嗨 麦克斯      小野洋子
Hi Max.        Yoko.
我决定自己去明斯克
I've decided to go to Minsk without you.
哇
Wow
少了你一切都会不同
It won't be the same.
但至少明斯克不会变
but it will still be Minsk.
新年快乐
Happy New Year.
你还好吧?
Are you all right?
我没事 没事
Yeah, I'm fine. I'm fine.
你要去明斯克
You're going to Minsk.
不 我不要去明斯克
No, I'm not going to Minsk.
你一定要去明斯克
Oh, you are so going to Minsk.
你属于明斯克 不能为了我留在这里
You belong in Minsk. You can't stay here just because of me.
我可以 如果去 我就得和你分手
Yes, I can. Because if I go, it means I have to break up with you.
我不能和你分手      可以 你可以
And I can't break up with you.        Oh, yes, yes, yes you can.
你只要说 "菲比 我爱你 但工作就是我的生命
Just say, uh "Phoebe, I love you, but my work is my life.
我现在只能这么做"
And that's what I have to do right now.
我会说 "你的工作? 你怎么能那么说?"
And I say, "Your work? Your work? How can you say that?"
然后你说 "我的心都碎了
And then you say, urn "It's tearing me apart
但我别无选择 你能理解吗?
but I have no choice. Can't you understand that?"
我会说 "不 我无法理解解
And I say, "No. No. I can't understand that."
嗷      对不起
Uh. ow.        Sorry. Urn
然后你抱住我
And, and then you put your arms around me
你抱住我      抱歉
And then you put your arms around me.        Oh, oh. Sorry.
然后你说你爱我 永远不会忘记我
And, urn, and then you tell me that you love me and you'll never forget me.
我永远都不会忘记你
I'll never forget you.
然后说已经午夜了 你得走了
And then you say that it's almost midnight and you have to go
因为你想如果不能完成它
because you don't want to start the new year with me
就无法和我开始新的一年
if you can't finish it.
我会想你的
I'm gonna miss you
科学家
you scientist guy.
我们在时代广场为您实况报导
Hi, this is Dick Clark, live in Times Square.
时代广场的五彩纸片纷纷落下
We're in a virtual snowstorm of confetti here in Times Square.
一年比一年盛大
It gets bigger and better every year
好了 孩子们
Here you go, kids.
然后孔雀就咬了我
And then the peacock bit me. Ha, ha.
请你在午夜时吻我
Please kiss me at midnight.
你看到珊蒂了吗?      我不知道怎么说
You seen Sandy?        Ooh. Uh, I don't know how to tell you this...
她和麦克斯 在摩妮卡的房间里 那个科学怪人
but she's in Monica's bedroom, getting it on with Max, that scientist geek.
你看 我还是告诉你了
Oh, look at that. I did know how to tell you.
嘿 各位 球要落下了
Hey, everybody, the ball is going.
什么?
What?
球要落下了
The ball is dropping.
再过二十秒就是午夜
In 20 seconds, it'll be midnight.
兴奋的时刻即将到来
And the moment of joy is upon us.
看来"不约会的约定"奏效了
Looks like that "no date pact" thing worked out.
大家看起来都很开心 我讨厌这样
Everybody looks so happy. I hate that.
不是每个人都开心 嘿 巴比
Not everybody is happy. Hey, Bobby.
一 新年快乐
One. Happy New Year!
这么说好了 我不是数学大师
You know, I uh, just thought I'd throw this out there. I'm no math whiz
但是这儿有三男三女
but I do believe there are three girls and three guys right here.
噢 我今晚谁都不想亲
Oh. I don't feel like kissing anyone tonight.
我谁都不能亲
I can't kiss anyone.
所以我要亲每个人?
So I'm kissing everyone?
不 你不能亲罗斯 他是你哥
No, no, no. You can't kiss Ross. That's your brother.
太好了 大家都能亲到 除了我
Perfect. Perfect. So now everybody's getting kissed but me.
好吧 谁来亲我?
All right. Somebody kiss me.
谁来亲我 已经午夜了 快来亲我 已经午夜了
Somebody kiss me.It's midnight. Somebody kiss me. It's midnight.
好吧 好吧 好吧
All right. All right. All right.
亲了
There.
我真的希望能成功
I wanted this to work so much.
我很投入 你知道么
I mean I'm still in there, you know?
帮他换尿布 抓跳蚤
Changing his diapers. Picking his fleas.
但他却视为理所当然
But he's just phoning it in.
真的很难接受这个事实 深爱某人却
Just so hard to accept the fact that something you love so much
却得不到回报
doesn't love you back, you know?
我想那贱人打断了我的牙齿
I think that bitch cracked my tooth.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
海盗编号：HDT10-P1-24-10-01-1212